still valuable beginning of the last of
最后的开始仍然有价值
the date of extraordinary antipathy
非常反感的日期
tokio super williams take that the wall
东京超级威廉姆斯把那堵墙
project single javi varas cinema
Project Single哈维·瓦拉斯电影院
but even in kavala identity
但即使在卡瓦拉身份中
[Music]
[音乐]
[Laughter]
[笑声]
with the opportunity to give in studios
有机会进入工作室
master on my name is stefan schlott
我名字的主人是斯蒂芬·施洛特
a working in the company called the
在公司工作的
one in Stuttgart a software
斯图加特一个软件
development consulting and security and
发展咨询与安全
technical academy in washington
华盛顿技术学院
monsters instances created the the
怪物实例创建了
update label update
更新标签更新
[Music]
[音乐]
the captains worked
队长们工作了
these objects pence too
这些物品也便
use cases by rita weis the instant
Rita Weis的用例即刻
messaging services of the grand instance
大型实例的消息传递服务
properties of discussion shuttle service
讨论班车服务的属性
service instant replay testing and
服务即时重播测试和
design services and services
设计服务及服务
clubs the penan jackson
潘南·杰克逊俱乐部
the daily life in concentra- ple has from
集中的日常生活来自
now as in concz business information
现在就像在concz商业信息中一样
there is 19 formation what happened
有19个阵型发生了什么
Alsace in the house stolen service center
阿尔萨斯在房屋被盗服务中心
small happening anthropology
小事人类学
construct situation so logins nice and
构建情况，因此登录很好，
have a look at the example which is not
看看不是的例子
just implementing output very
只是非常实现输出
nice but can take aways of the company
不错，但是可以带走公司
vitalogic lombok job in the library in
在图书馆的简历 lombok 工作
more
更多
n / A
良好
[Music]
[音乐]
well ok or c let's take another
好吧，还是c，我们再来个
example hamborn is in you are in clever
例子hamborn在你里面很聪明
Stops a multi threading is in the
停止多线程在
keep it simple invest example of his
保持简单的投资例子
implementing racing course of the data
实施数据竞赛
objects hobbies person hobbies by
对象的爱好人的爱好
database access to
数据库访问
zoom is floating phone data base is
缩放是浮动电话数据库是
novell implement aspect event
Novell工具方面的事件
logging tottenham
托特纳姆热刺队
the output offers the correct offer
输出提供正确的报价
panz pänz union opladen course you will
潘茨·潘茨联盟奥普拉登课程，您将
the clever news de www scher in blogs
博客中有关www scher的聪明新闻
statement to the value of the hobby securlog
业余爱好价值的声明
level is is the back of fire
水平是火的背后
the colt becomes a sibling pointer
小马驹成为同级指针
exception so in case you just look
例外，以防万一你只是看
for something stupid ingo just a game
为了一些愚蠢的游戏而已
machine loki video training training on
机器loki视频培训培训
the lok level to 71 double you get
乐高达到71倍
enough and accepted from somewhere
足够并从某个地方接受
desire is completely the other people
欲望完全是其他人
your problem but very end like that
你的问题，但最终会这样
[Music]
[音乐]
also considerably for program change
对于程序更改也很重要
would not go but while the tail risk
不会走，但尾巴风险
office of data base could protect
数据库办公室可以保护
exception
例外
so let's just leave the messeturm's return
所以让我们离开信使的归来吧
is definitely that and of course that they are
肯定是的，当然他们是
should be evil eyes hobbies like that
应该是邪恶的眼睛爱好
henzler is fine because of that
亨茨勒很好，因为
Kabul give her hand ok and the rest
喀布尔让她的手好，其余的
is at the side of the women
在女人的身边
The program is running is celebrating
该程序正在庆祝
if the dredger helper opens it up
如果挖泥船帮手将其打开
the program
该程序
these cost the dredge users and events
这些花费了疏users用户和事件
to string and europe second to print out
紧随其后，欧洲第二次打印出来
day content object using the string
日内容对象使用字符串
lombok smart and went rating so
lombok 聪明，去评级，所以
lombok completely the heater so what is
lombok 完全加热器，那是什么
it that way around the parameter uk pass
以这种方式绕过参数uk pass
to cover up notation and if that
掩盖符号，如果那
Slapping on more advanced is that
拍下更高级的是
nati on
纳蒂
most of the time it's probably been
大多数时候可能是
reported by
报告者
orient fekters correctly executed
定向fekters正确执行
steven correct coach in just because
史蒂芬正确的教练只是因为
we're very special
我们很特别
This will be the fine interface and
这将是很好的界面，
solution support act in the ketscher
解决方案支持法案
macho macho generic way to catch
大男子主义通用方式赶上
exception second if you are after
如果您之后则例外
technologies los angeles
技术洛杉矶
just what we tab ramos faction chief
这就是我们所选择的拉莫斯派系首领
klaas jan polacek exception of jsa
克拉斯·扬·波拉切克（Jla）例外
Pursuit trades in the qet
追求交易
clarify statement
澄清声明
your heart is built up that is
你的心是建立的
for people's hands on the hand
为了人们的手
put
放
the cinemas problem
电影院问题
that's clear
很清楚
someone who tried to be extra smart
试图变得更加聪明的人
something huge calculation trick huge
巨大的计算技巧
amount of memory and out of memory and
内存量和内存不足
obviously in east tyrol
显然在东蒂罗尔
jessica exception exception catch a fire
杰西卡（Jessica）异常异常着火
you can not handle
你无法处理
this is better we're giving away four
更好的是我们送了四个
putting six is ​​ok of recovery
放六个就可以恢复
situation of switzerland on the finger and the
手指和瑞士的情况
partners okay it's not the intended but
合作伙伴好吧，这不是预期的，但
you can display solutions something like
您可以显示类似的解决方案
that's you for your business
那是你的事
something the exception handling the
一些异常处理
sessions roaming an exception which is
会话漫游异常是
yahoo extraction levels something about
雅虎提取级别有关
you logic what's not very proud to keep
你认为保留什么不是很自豪
some description string thing is
一些描述字符串是
watching the exception
看着异常
exception you just got here
你刚到这里就例外
there are sect races the cost if
有宗派比赛的代价是
looking at the box we have output
看着我们有输出的盒子
have the know how of the stack trace
了解堆栈跟踪的方式
valentyn dislike button a poison of
valentyn不喜欢纽扣
discussion effect exceptions a general
讨论效果例外
idea and
想法和
just another thing about exception
关于异常的另一件事
handling and lodging one love not and
处理和寄宿一个爱不是
the pointer sisters perfect that boeing
指针姐妹完美的波音
an exception that has description
具有描述的异常
relieves exception here walking and
缓解这里走路的异常
walking to w as in mario pine best
最好去马里奥·派恩
way to developing and accepting
发展和接受的方式
also gladly in my cat statement villa
也很高兴在我的猫声明别墅中
exception elicit it in ketch in the
异常导致它在ketch中
exception somewhere in time handling it
在处理它的某个时间出现异常
in some way dates in the program or
以某种方式显示程序中的日期或
display message of doing some other
显示其他信息
Recovery service point via lok like
通过lok之类的恢复服务点
exception the machines are completely stacked
机器完全堆叠在一起
trace exceptions implementation object
跟踪异常实现对象
and subject flying objects as well as robert
以及飞行物体和罗伯特
euro play no something else would you
欧元玩，别无选择
can not return of play superhero as well
也不能返回超级英雄
scrolling exception exception return
滚动异常异常返回
values ​​and extranet extremely one
价值观和企业外部网极一
portfolios injection zf delivers the app
投资组合注入zf提供了该应用程序
give behind but example of
放弃但以身作则
exceptions is happy intermediate result
例外是快乐的中间结果
venture second life for control smart
控制智慧的第二人生
this is change for example discovery
这是变化，例如发现
lotto king mod service check in about
乐透王mod服务签入
equal
平等
good in the session well so
会议很好，所以
action star jackie a virtual
动作明星杰基虚拟
supergrass and jus accepted
超级草和强制接受
accounting and leaseback program
会计和回租计划
problem
问题
okay though their vices are large area
好的，尽管他们的恶习很大
[Music]
[音乐]
creating the interface
创建界面
the process to the process as copy and
流程复制到流程
increased the cisco systems austria
增加了cisco系统奥地利
keeper single instance and
守护者单实例和
Implementation of identity implemented
实施身份实施
okay but design beds workshop are like that
好的，但是设计床工作坊就是这样
that is it factory in the design
那是设计中的工厂
patterns workshops creative factory and
图案工场创意工厂
luxury cars single can not dance in the
豪华车单身不能跳舞
class and drive from the class single
班级和单班开车
Objects became property of the instant
对象成为当下的财产
solic rated once the return of the news
索利克斯被定为新闻回归
tribune of creative factory in
创意工厂论坛
combination single instance
组合单实例
[Music]
[音乐]
enjoy the opening round robin ii
享受开幕式robin ii
[Applause]
[鼓掌]